▶ the real client against the real service
  ✔ indexApi.status() resolves and returns the declared shape (4.0062ms)
  ✔ indexApi.price(1) resolves -- so `?limit=1` is a request the service accepts (1.1275ms)
  ✔ indexApi.candles(60, 5000) resolves -- so `?bucket=60&limit=5000` is accepted (13.3976ms)
  ✔ indexApi.events() resolves and the query string is accepted (1.6823ms)
  ✔ indexApi.summary() resolves -- the endpoint whose TYPE was fiction for a while (1.1525ms)
  ✔ an over-cap `limit` is CLAMPED and the clamp is DISCLOSED, not an error (22.6722ms)
  ✔ `limit=0` is accepted and returns nothing, which is a different thing from an error (1.4049ms)

  Residual gaps in the fetch double's cross-check:
    - the client's `cache: 'no-store'` header is NOT observable from here
    - transport failures (timeout, TLS, DNS) are NOT exercised -- only a 400 was
    - the double supports string | URL | Request inputs, but only string is exercised
    - Node version changes can alter TypeError wording, which the client string-matches

  ✔ a NON-NUMERIC parameter IS refused, and classified as refused (0.8922ms)
✔ the real client against the real service (47.3738ms)
▶ what this cross-check still cannot show
  ✔ records the residual gaps rather than implying full coverage (0.1258ms)
✔ what this cross-check still cannot show (0.428ms)
ℹ tests 9
ℹ suites 2
ℹ pass 9
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 50.2927
