Not run here (need live services, run explicitly): api-against-real-service.test.ts, contract-live.test.ts

========================================================================
api.test.ts
========================================================================
▶ endpoints
  ✔ defaults to the ports the services actually use (0.4642ms)
  ✔ honours the environment override and strips a trailing slash (0.1519ms)
  ✔ always produces an absolute URL on the server (0.2063ms)
✔ endpoints (1.836ms)
▶ indexApi -- request construction
  ✔ requests an ABSOLUTE url, which is the fix for the server-side 500 (10.8759ms)
  ✔ builds the query strings the service documents (0.7865ms)
  ✔ defaults the event limit and omits an absent kind (0.8086ms)
  ✔ sends no-store, because a cached console shows stale figures as current (0.2416ms)
✔ indexApi -- request construction (12.8621ms)
▶ indexApi -- failure classification
  ✔ names an unbuilt request URL as a console bug, not a service that is down (0.2215ms)
  ✔ names a transport failure as unreachable, and says how to start the service (0.168ms)
  ✔ surfaces the service's own refusal verbatim rather than rewriting it (0.2634ms)
  ✔ describes a non-JSON error body as a proxy answering, which is what it is (0.2774ms)
  ✔ catches a 200 that is not JSON -- a rewritten page, not data (0.2527ms)
  ✔ marks a 400 as not retryable and a 500 as retryable (0.1049ms)
  ✔ does not retry: exactly one request per call, however it fails (0.1019ms)
✔ indexApi -- failure classification (1.527ms)
ℹ tests 14
ℹ suites 3
ℹ pass 14
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 19.9701

========================================================================
chart-geometry.test.ts
========================================================================
▶ computeRange -- the zero-range guard
  ✔ expands a flat range instead of dividing by zero (0.938ms)
  ✔ every y coordinate is finite for a flat series -- the assertion the bug would fail (0.0939ms)
  ✔ keeps a zero price drawable (0.0811ms)
  ✔ pads a range that has movement, without making it flat (0.0729ms)
  ✔ distinguishes flat from padded -- a one-base-unit move is not flat (0.0524ms)
  ✔ returns null when there is nothing finite to scale (0.0428ms)
  ✔ ignores non-finite values when finite ones exist (0.0486ms)
  ✔ handles a negative range (a price cannot be negative, but the guard must not assume it) (0.0473ms)
✔ computeRange -- the zero-range guard (1.9203ms)
▶ rangeFor
  ✔ scales over all four values of every candle, not just the closes (0.1222ms)
  ✔ returns null for an empty series so the component renders its empty state (0.0795ms)
  ✔ reads the exact decimal strings, which for this vault are all "1.1" (0.2137ms)
✔ rangeFor (0.5069ms)
▶ makeScale
  ✔ maps the range maximum to the top of the band and the minimum to the bottom (0.093ms)
  ✔ is monotonic: a higher price is never drawn lower (0.0548ms)
✔ makeScale (0.1856ms)
▶ candleGeometry -- the doji floor
  ✔ gives a zero-height body (a doji) a visible minimum (0.1642ms)
  ✔ uses the true height when the candle did move (0.0484ms)
  ✔ marks up and down from open vs close, not high vs low (0.0367ms)
  ✔ treats close === open as up, so a flat series is one colour rather than alternating (0.027ms)
  ✔ places the body top at the lesser of open and close (0.0281ms)
  ✔ produces a finite geometry for every candle in the real flat series (0.481ms)
✔ candleGeometry -- the doji floor (0.8694ms)
▶ horizontalLayout
  ✔ keeps a single candle from being drawn as a wall (0.0722ms)
  ✔ keeps five thousand candles from rounding away to nothing (0.0438ms)
  ✔ centres candle i in its own slot (0.0372ms)
  ✔ never produces a zero or negative width for any realistic count (0.0493ms)
✔ horizontalLayout (0.2574ms)
ℹ tests 23
ℹ suites 5
ℹ pass 23
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 8.4295

========================================================================
contract.test.ts
========================================================================
▶ fixture: /api/status
  ✔ has exactly the fields the console reads, and no others (0.7119ms)
  ✔ types each field the way `Status` declares it (0.111ms)
  ✔ carries a coverage object whose note is printed verbatim on the page (0.0908ms)
  ✔ reports the gap honestly: the series starts later than the deployment (0.1169ms)
✔ fixture: /api/status (1.5877ms)
▶ fixture: /api/price
  ✔ has exactly the declared fields (0.0905ms)
  ✔ keeps every amount a STRING, including the one that overflows a double (0.1009ms)
  ✔ documents that price is derived on read, not stored (0.0516ms)
✔ fixture: /api/price (0.3406ms)
▶ fixture: /api/candles
  ✔ has exactly the declared fields (0.1029ms)
  ✔ gives every candle eight fields, all of the declared type (0.6992ms)
  ✔ keeps OHLC ordered: low <= open,close <= high (0.6362ms)
  ✔ every candle in the captured window is flat at 1.1 -- the reason the chart guard exists (0.119ms)
  ✔ explains that `limit` is blocks pulled, not candles returned (0.1254ms)
✔ fixture: /api/candles (1.835ms)
▶ fixture: /api/summary
  ✔ has exactly the declared fields -- the ones this console originally got wrong (0.5148ms)
  ✔ keys event kinds by name, each with a count and an exact asset sum (0.2751ms)
  ✔ totals the counts to totalEvents (0.3329ms)
  ✔ reconciles to the vault's total assets -- gross in, minus gross out, plus reported yield (0.8898ms)
  ✔ the naive per-kind sum does NOT equal totalAssets, and the difference is the trap (0.0819ms)
  ✔ has no unknown kinds, so the decoder covers every log the vault emits (0.0347ms)
✔ fixture: /api/summary (2.3517ms)
▶ cross-fixture consistency
  ✔ the same vault and chain appear in every fixture that names them (0.6415ms)
  ✔ the asset decimals agree across every fixture (0.8898ms)
  ✔ the summary flow identity equals the price series' last totalAssets (0.4479ms)
✔ cross-fixture consistency (2.0456ms)
ℹ tests 21
ℹ suites 5
ℹ pass 21
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 14.4538

========================================================================
format.test.ts
========================================================================
▶ parseAmount -- decimal string to base units
  ✔ reads a decimal string as exact base units (0.4876ms)
  ✔ handles a fraction shorter than the asset has decimals (0.0671ms)
  ✔ treats a trailing dot as a whole number (0.0518ms)
  ✔ carries the sign (0.0464ms)
  ✔ REFUSES more fraction digits than the asset has, rather than truncating (0.2308ms)
  ✔ rejects anything that is not a plain decimal (0.1182ms)
  ✔ accepts surrounding whitespace rather than making every caller trim (0.0735ms)
  ✔ rejects a decimals count that is not a non-negative integer (0.1432ms)
✔ parseAmount -- decimal string to base units (1.7792ms)
▶ formatBigInt / formatBaseUnits -- RAW BASE UNITS to a decimal string
  ✔ converts the vault's real share supply, which no double can hold (0.2388ms)
  ✔ trims trailing zeros so one number prints one way (0.1351ms)
  ✔ pads a fraction correctly at 18 decimals (0.0574ms)
  ✔ keeps the sign (0.0294ms)
  ✔ handles a magnitude AND a nonzero tail, the worst case for a double (0.0247ms)
  ✔ accepts a bigint as well as a string, without changing the answer (0.043ms)
  ✔ REFUSES a decimal string -- that input means the caller grabbed the wrong formatter (0.0744ms)
  ✔ rejects a decimals count that is not a non-negative integer (0.043ms)
✔ formatBigInt / formatBaseUnits -- RAW BASE UNITS to a decimal string (0.7992ms)
▶ formatDecimal -- an ALREADY-formatted decimal string
  ✔ passes a price through unchanged (0.1323ms)
  ✔ normalises trailing zeros so one candle's four values print alike (0.0366ms)
  ✔ tolerates surrounding whitespace (0.0226ms)
  ✔ passes a whole-number price through, because "2" is a legal price (0.0247ms)
  ✔ rejects anything that is not a decimal (0.0855ms)
  ✔ THE PAIR IS ASYMMETRIC ON PURPOSE, and the asymmetry is the protection (0.043ms)
✔ formatDecimal -- an ALREADY-formatted decimal string (0.4126ms)
▶ groupThousands
  ✔ groups the integer part only (0.1046ms)
  ✔ leaves short numbers and negatives alone (0.0371ms)
  ✔ does not group the fraction (0.0225ms)
✔ groupThousands (0.2078ms)
▶ displayBaseUnits -- the chain's raw amounts, ready for the page
  ✔ renders the chained totalAssets in whole units (0.1112ms)
  ✔ groups the integer part of a large raw amount (0.0362ms)
  ✔ renders the 19-digit share supply as SHARES, not as raw base units (0.0342ms)
  ✔ can be asked for the ungrouped form (0.0321ms)
  ✔ shows an em dash for null -- an empty vault has no price, and 0 is a claim (0.0272ms)
  ✔ returns an unparseable amount UNCHANGED rather than hiding the evidence (0.0394ms)
✔ displayBaseUnits -- the chain's raw amounts, ready for the page (0.3542ms)
▶ displayDecimal -- the service's formatted amounts, ready for the page
  ✔ renders a price (0.0898ms)
  ✔ renders a candle value with an 18-digit tail (0.029ms)
  ✔ groups by default and can be asked not to -- even for a uint256-shaped value (0.0339ms)
  ✔ shows an em dash for null (0.0221ms)
  ✔ returns a malformed value unchanged, so the disagreement stays visible (0.0304ms)
✔ displayDecimal -- the service's formatted amounts, ready for the page (0.267ms)
▶ sharePercent
  ✔ computes a percentage in BigInt for magnitudes a double cannot divide (0.0718ms)
  ✔ truncates rather than rounds, so it can never read as more than the truth (0.0443ms)
  ✔ returns null when there is no total to take a share of (0.0359ms)
  ✔ returns null for values that are not integers (0.069ms)
  ✔ survives 18-decimal share counts (0.0543ms)
✔ sharePercent (0.3746ms)
▶ timeLabel and duration
  ✔ formats a timestamp as zero-padded local HH:MM (0.5524ms)
  ✔ formats durations at each unit boundary (0.0584ms)
  ✔ shows an em dash for an unknown duration (0.0406ms)
✔ timeLabel and duration (0.7058ms)
▶ shortenAddress
  ✔ keeps enough of an address to recognise it (0.0505ms)
  ✔ handles null and short input without throwing (0.0276ms)
✔ shortenAddress (0.1117ms)
ℹ tests 46
ℹ suites 9
ℹ pass 46
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 10.972

========================================================================
4/4 test files passed
all green
